Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Like I said, we've decided to put you in the field.
Alright, our first mission.
Here we go.
So, what are we doing?
I assume it's something befitting royalty such as myself?
Yeah, it's a real honor. Go to Saucy Village for some boar hunting.
Huh? Hunting boar?
That is a terrible mission.
No, it's not! You take that back!
I can break down a boar with my bare hands! Easy!
No, you can't! Don't even think about trying!
Either go or die. Your choice.
We'll go!
So what if it's boar hunting?
We're finally going on a mission!
I'm getting pumped now!
Yeah!
I still don't see why you would be sending me.
Come on!
Do you ever do anything but complain?
Actually, that wasn't intended as a complaint.
It's just, given that I can't control my magic power,
should I really be going on a mission at all?
Here it is!
Introducing Greer the Cyclone!
So cool!
I know, right? Awesome, isn't it?
Yeah!
It's lame!
A man never goes back on his word!
Let's do this thing!
Fly!
Oh yeah!
This is amazing, Magna!
We're one with the wind!
Rasta!
Are you trying to die or something?
Hold on!
Right!
So it's here, is it?
The magic stone.
Find it.
Sir!
In the mist, be lost.
In the mist, I only won.
On geliyor everything with a heartbeat.
I kept it.
I can't say before...
Yeah, after that's it.
Let's pour on.
Be sure to really give this sort of inspiration.
Oh my God, I'm aýっver typist,
Thank you.
Magna, don't you think we should be helping him?
I'm not doing anything until I've rested up a little.
You know how much work it was flying you two out here?
It's like a whole freaking lot of magic and muscle.
Ah, it'll be okay.
Rust is a sturdy guy.
Yes, but...
If you're so worried, then go help him.
I ain't gonna stop you.
Here we go.
Why me?
I got you now!
Finally finished him off.
You got him.
Not bad, right?
But the fun's not over yet.
Now that's what I call good huntin'!
Another display of your freakish strength.
Please!
A few of these pigs is nothing!
Child's play!
You really are something else.
Well, if this doesn't please Sehi, I don't know what will.
Yeah, big piggy party tonight!
So wait.
The chief of Saucy Village.
Sehi?
He's a friend of yours?
Yeah, me and the old man go way back.
You see, Raaka Village, where I come from, isn't far from here.
We're practically neighbors.
I used to get into all kinds of trouble when I was a kid.
Yeah, used to.
That's changed how?
When I got my grimoire, the sense of power totally went to my head.
I flew into Saucy Alkaki thinking I was gonna take over the place or something.
Boy, was I wrong!
Get, get, get, get, get, get, get!
Get, get, get, get!
Get that!
Hey, what do you think you're doing to my village, you little brat?
Ha!
You looking for a beating, old man?
Let's go!
Not a chance.
I won't be the one getting a beating today.
Oh, you think so?
Yeah, I do!
Ah, crap!
This'll teach you!
We're not done.
Wait, what?
You've earned yourself a spanky.
Ah, damn it, damn it!
What are you doing to me?
Didn't stop me, though.
I took him on a whole bunch of times after that.
Game on you!
A real man doesn't attack people without reason!
Protecting the weak from those who would hurt them.
That's what a real man does!
Golden!
Another thing!
A real man doesn't make anyone worry!
Nobody knew how to put me in my place like he did.
Sounds strong.
Yeah.
Oh, he absolutely is.
Matter of fact, I found out later that when old Sehi was young, he had enough power to try out for the Magic Knights.
You know, he's actually the one who told me I should think about taking the entrance exam in the first place.
Not bad. Looks like you can just about hold your own now, boy.
Yeah, I've got a better handle on how to use my grimoire these days.
I agree. Which means, you might be ready to take the Magic Knights entrance exam.
What? Me? Oh, man, are you going crazy?
Why not? You've got what it takes.
Yeah, right.
Like a commoner from the middle of nowhere even stands a chance.
Nothing's set in stone!
So you're a commoner from way out in the sticks. What's that got to do with anything?
You use your power to build your own future.
I couldn't make that dream come true.
But you can.
Really?
Become a man. It's time.
So, what do the Magic Knights do anyway?
You don't even know that much!
Ow!
No question. It's all thanks to him that I am who I am today.
Obviously, I wound up passing the entrance exam.
And when I did, no one was happier than Sehi.
Sounds like a nice guy.
You bet.
I know part of the reason he came to the capital was to make a fortune that he could bring back to help improve his village,
but I have a feeling he wanted to see me, too.
Of course, in the end, he took me for all I had.
I'll never forget that he's the one who taught me about being a real man.
I want to be as good a guy as he is someday.
I respect him more than anyone, except for y'all...
What's up? Something wrong?
What the hell's going on?
The whole village?
It's covered in mist.
They've got some pretty weird weather around here, huh?
It's not the weather, idiot. It's magic.
It is?
Wow, a magic mist.
Trying to make it through that would be about as effective as walking around blindfolded.
We'd lose all sense of direction and blunder around the place helplessly.
Magic that can completely cover an entire village.
A spell this powerful didn't come from any villager.
And it sure as hell ain't Sehi's magic either.
Something bad happened here.
Hey, Asta.
Sir!
Use your sword and cut through this mist.
Yes, sir!
Aw, you're just being silly, Magna.
You can't cut through mist with a sword.
I'll give you silly, you punk!
You can cut through magic with that sword of yours, can't you?
Oh, yeah!
That's right!
Yeah!
Okay!
Push forward!
Let's go!
Got it!
To the right!
Roger!
Hang a left!
Yes, sir!
You do know this place pretty well.
That's right.
Left!
Yep!
You feel that?
Yeah, I did.
It's magic.
And it's strong.
Straight ahead now!
Be careful!
Right!
We should be in the square.
Yeah!
Kill them!
It's three of the magic knights.
I can't believe they came to save us.
Magna, is that you?
Hey, Nick, what the heck's going on?
Hey, come on!
Stay with me, old man!
No, please.
He can't be gone.
He was just protecting us.
They're here just like you said, Grandpa.
The magic knights showed up.
We'll be safe now.
Your prayers were hurt.
To kill someone?
Just like that?
Are you the one who's responsible?
You've thrown off my schedule.
I don't appreciate that.
Ten seconds from now, everyone here will die.
Damn.
I don't have enough power.
Oster?
Think again.
Why would you want to do something so horrible?
Who do you think you are?
They don't look like Diamond Kingdom spies.
Or savages come to shake down the place.
So who the hell are they?
I haven't heard that any of the magic knights were going to be in the area.
Perhaps they're here on an unofficial mission.
Another thing I'd like to know.
How did they manage to tear their way through the mist and enter the village?
The Black Bulls.
The roughest, most undisciplined, most heretical of all the magic knight squads.
Dealing with this riffraff would be a waste of precious time.
Five minutes.
Now, we will dispose of these useless villagers in a manner befitting their station.
And then we'll find what we came for.
Do you really think you can ignore us?
Mist Magic Shroud.
Illusory Mist.
If you think we will allow you to approach Master Heat so easily, you are a fool.
In the mist, be lost.
You're the ones who need to get lost!
So that's how he was able to cut through my ice magic earlier.
I don't know what kind of magic it is.
But that large sword of his can nullify spells.
I can't have him getting too close.
I asked you why you tried to massacre these villagers and I want an answer now!
Huh.
In this kingdom there are three regions divided by inhabitants.
The noble realm where the nobility reside.
The common realm where the citizenry live.
And the Forsaken Realm.
Yeah.
A saucy village is in the Forsaken Realm.
Most in this realm are of inferior stock.
They are capable of performing only a few meager spells to help with the drudgery of their everyday lives.
They are much like beasts that cannot use tools.
You asked why I intend to do away with the villagers.
I am merely attempting to dispose of the useless beasts that might waste my time.
Useless beasts?!
Consider yourself.
You have enough magic power to have joined the magic knights.
You must attempt to save them because that is your duty.
But surely you can see what insignificant creatures they truly are.
The folks in the upper realms sure have it made.
Living a good life while we work our hands to the bone.
If they're so jealous why don't they just move there?
Well that's much easier said than done.
Really?
Why?
Only those with powerful magic can live in the upper realms.
They look down upon those who have less magic power.
Despite the fact that all of us are human.
Well, I'm gonna join a magic knight squad.
Then, I'm gonna become the wizard king.
And when I am, I'll make sure nobody gets looked down on for having weak magic.
That sounds lovely.
If it were easy enough for you to do it, already be done.
What did you just say to me?!
You should respect your elders!
Come on, you could never even be a magic knight, much less the wizard king.
You don't have any magic power.
You may think they're nothing but useless beasts.
But I'll do whatever I have to to protect them!
Interesting.
These pathetic little animals are truly that important to you.
I'll send that ice right back to-
What is this?
Ice and Mist Compound Magic. Endless Ice Cage.
Do you imagine you can still protect your herd of beasts like this?
I have never been particularly fond of doing things slowly but surely.
However, this would seem to be the most effective method.
Cluster!
Thaw Ice.
So it can not only cancel magic, that sword of yours can reflect it as well.
But you're a fool if you think that will defeat me.
I can create wave after wave of icy fangs.
Go on.
Let's see you protect them.
Damn this guy!
Austin and I have our hands full keeping the villagers safe.
What's more, my magic is starting to run out.
We're up against four guys powerful enough to be magic knights.
And I have a feeling that one still hasn't shown us everything he can do.
This is turning out to be a hell of a first mission for those two.
Things are going south quick.
And if all that was enough to make me give up, I wouldn't be a man!
Here we go!
Your fellow commoner is gonna keep you safe and sound!
Mecca!
How long can they hold out?
A magic knight who can't even control her magic properly.
The Black Bulls must truly be desperate to have accepted this one.
Such fragile beasts incapable even of protecting themselves.
Forsaking them will be your salvation, magic knights.
Go now and live!
And abandon them? Not a chance!
A real man doesn't give up on anyone, no matter how bad it gets!
What's wrong with me?
Even though I'm royalty.
Even though I have more magic power than anyone here.
Stay behind us, Noelle!
I'm only holding the others back.
There's no point to me being here.
Forsaking them will be your salvation, magic knights.
That's right. I am royalty.
I can't die in some backwater village.
I'll go. Just leave and...
Miss Magic Knight, please help us!
We need you!
This little girl is looking me in the eye and begging for help.
I have to protect her!
That looks like...
A new spell?
I won't run!
Never!
I will protect them! I am royalty!
What's more...
I am a member of the Black Bulls!
I will protect them!
I am royalty!
What's more...
I am a member of the Black Bulls!
I will protect them! I am royalty! What's more, I am a member of the Black Bulls!
I am a member of the Black Bulls! I am a member of the Black Bulls!
It's strange, it's weird.
If you want to laugh, you'll be fine.
I want to be what you want to do.
I want to be the same morning.
I want to be the same tomorrow.
Oink, oink, oink, grab, grab, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink, oink.
Hey, now, it's okay.
Just don't do it again.
Oink, oink.
Oink, oink, oink, oink.
Your pigs take care, okay?
Oink.
That was amazing, Noelle!
Just don't give up and you'll be fine.
We'll keep them all safe.
Don't worry.
Black Clover, page 10.
Guardians.
My magic is never giving up!